

## **PROFILE**

Hello, my name is Paula Valencia I'm an Interactive Media Designer from Colombia. I describe myself as a perseverant person, I enjoy learning new things and my passion is to learn from Japanese culture.

During my professional path, I have developed skills that make me able to work with User Experience, Graphic Design, Web Design, App Development, and Video Editing.

My main social skills are composed of high adaptability, teamwork, and time management.

# **CONTACT ME**

- +57 304 590 2690
- @ tona.valencia@hotmail.com
- http www.tonavalencia.github.io

# **EDUCATION**

2020 PLATZI UX Pro

UX Process Management February 2020 Video Game Design February 2020 Flutter August 2020

ICESI UNIVERSITY
Interactive Media Designer
July 2013 - August 2018

2018 MITSUE-LINKS CO .LTD
UX Research Internship
April 2018 - July 2018

NIHON UNIVERSITY
International Exchange Student
September 2016 - February 2017

## **EXPERIENCE**

2020

CORPORACIÓN TALENTUM

Analist - Developer July 2019 - Present
Requirements analyst and game developer in a
corporation that works with the Government of El
Valle. With my team, we develop educational games
with the purpose to encourage the use of technology
in an educational environment for populations with
low resources.

FOSFENOS MEDIA - EL SALVADOR'S MINISTRY OF EDUCATION

Interactive Desginer March 2019 - May 2019
Web development and design for the brand new animated program Historias en Juego presented on the educational television channel TATUKATV. http://tatukatv.sv/historias-en-juego

MITSUE- LINKS CO. LTD

2018 UX Research Intern April 2018 - July 2018

Research intern for user experience. Worked with user tests, project reports, blog writings, cultural differences, and research findings.

https://www.mitsue.co.jp/english/global\_ux/blog/2 01805/16\_1800.html

**IOL COLOMBIA** 

Main Designer - July 2015 / July 2017
Responsible for the design of brand, development and web design, graphic design of promotional pieces, management of social network.

## **LANGUAGES**

2017





